Okay, now that you have the basic ideas of function call semantics,
好了，既然你已经掌握了函数调用语义的基本概念，那
let us see them in action.
就让我们来看看它们的实际应用。
We have three functions here.
我们这里有三个函数。
My function, f and main.
我的函数，f 和 main。
As you have learned, we start execution of a program inside of main.
如你所知，我们开始在 main 中执行一个程序。
We've drawn a frame for main and
我们已经为 main 画了一个框架，
are ready to begin executing its first statement which declares the variable a.
准备开始执行它的第一个声明变量 a 的语句。
So we create its box inside of the frame for main.
所以我们在框架内为 main 创建了它的方框。
Next, we're going to set a equal to the value of the function call,
接下来，我们将设置一个等于函数调用的值，
myFunction of 3, 7.
myFunction 为 3、7。
To evaluate this expression, we need to create a frame for
要评估这个表达式，我们需要为
the function that we are calling, in this case, myFunction.
我们正在调用的函数（在本例中为 MyFunction）创建一个框架。
This will hold the parameters and variables of myFunction.
这将保存 myFunction 的参数和变量。
Next, we pass the parameters to myFunction.
接下来，我们将参数传递给 myFunction。
We create a box for
我们为
each parameter with the names coming from the functional declaration x and y.
每个参数创建一个方框，其名称来自函数声明 x 和 y。
We initialize these by copying in the values of the expressions
我们通过复制
that were passed, here, 3 and 7.
传递的表达式的值来初始化它们，这里，分别是 3 和 7。
Next, we need to note where to return when we finish executing myFunction.
接下来，我们需要记下当我们完成执行 myFunction 后要返回到哪里。
This location in the code is named the call site,
代码中的这个位置被命名为调用站点
the place where the function was called.
，即函数被调用的地方。
We'll note it with marker 1 in the code, and
我们将在代码中用标记 1 记下来，然后
put the same marker in the corner of the frame.
在框架的角落放置相同的标记。
Finally, we move the execution arrow into myFunction, and
最后，我们将执行箭头移到 MyFunction 中，然后
start executing code there.
开始在那里执行代码。
Here, we declare and initialize z, evaluating the expression, 2 times x-y.
在这里，我们声明并初始化 z，计算表达式，2 次 x-y。
The values for x and y come from the frame for myFunction, 3 and
x 和 y 的值分别来自 myFunction 的框架，
7 respectively, so z will be negative 1.
分别是 3 和 7，因此 z 将为负 1。
Now, we have reached a return statement.
现在，我们已经达成了退货声明。r@@
Return statements tell us to leave the current function
eturn 语句告诉我们让当前函数
returning to the call site noted in the frame.
返回到框架中注明的调用站点。
They also tell us the value to return to the caller.
它们还会告诉我们要返回给呼叫者的值。
The first thing we need to do is evaluate this expression to obtain
我们需要做的第一件事是评估这个表达式
the return value.
以获得返回值。
Here, the expression is z times x, so
这里，表达式是 z 乘以 x，所以
we evaluate negative 1 times 3 and get negative 3.
我们计算负数 1 乘以 3，得到负数 3。
Next, find where we should return.
接下来，找到我们应该返回的地方。
This is the call site we noted in the frame.
这是我们在框架中记录的呼叫地点。
Then we copy the return value back to the call site.
然后我们将返回值复制回调用站点。
The function call evaluates to this return value.
函数调用计算结果为该返回值。
We move the execution arrow back to the call site, and destroy the frame for
我们将执行箭头移回调用站点，然后销毁
the function we just returned from.
我们刚才返回的函数的框架。
Now, we are back in main.
现在，我们又回到了主场。
The call to myFunction evaluated to negative 3, so
对 myFunction 的调用计算结果为负 3，因此
this line behaves like a gets negative 3.
此行的行为类似于 a 变为负 3。
We finished that assignment putting negative 3 in a's box.
我们完成了任务，在 a 的盒子里放了负数 3。
Our next line again has a variable declaration and a function call.
我们的下一行又有一个变量声明和一个函数调用。
We make a box for b, and go through the same process to call f.
我们为 b 做一个盒子，然后通过同样的过程来调用 f。
We make a frame for f, and pass parameters.
我们为 f 做一个框架，然后传递参数。
This time, there's one parameter in whose value is a times a which is 9.
这次，有一个参数的值是乘以 a，也就是 9。
We note where to return and begin executing code inside of f.
我们记下从哪里返回并开始执行 f 中的代码。
Our next statement is a return statement, but
我们的下一个语句是 return 语句，但
the expression involves a function call.
表达式涉及函数调用。
So we have to evaluate that call before anything else.
因此，我们必须在其他任何事情之前先评估那个电话。
We start with a frame and past parameters.
我们从帧和过去的参数开始。
x gets the value of n which is 9, and y gets the value of n + 1 which is 10.
x 获取 n 的值，即 9，y 获得 n + 1 的值，即 10。
We note the call site.
我们记下了通话现场。
We use two this time since we are already using one somewhere else, and
这次我们使用两个，因为我们已经在其他地方使用了一个，然后
move the execution arrow to the start of myFunction, and
将执行箭头移到 MyFunction 的开头，然后
start executing code there.
开始在那里执行代码。
We declare Z and initialize it to 8.
我们声明 Z 并将其初始化为 8。
Now, we are ready to return from myFunction.
现在，我们已经准备好从 MyFunction 返回了。
We evaluate z times x which is 72.
我们评估 z 乘以 x，即 72。
Then we find that the call site noted in the frame and copy the return value there.
然后我们发现框架中记下的调用站点，并将返回值复制到那里。
Finally, we move the execution back
最后，我们将执行移回
to the call site destroying the frame from myFunction.
调用站点，销毁 MyFunction 中的帧。
Now, we pick up were we left off an f using 72 for
现在，我们继续前进 f，使用 72 作为对
the value of the call to myFunction.
myFunction 的调用的值。
We evaluate 3 + 72 to get 75.
我们评估 3 + 72 得到 75。
Since we are evaluating the return statement, this is the return value of f,
由于我们正在评估 return 语句，因此这是 f 的返回值，
so we find the call site and copy the return value there.
因此我们找到调用站点并将返回值复制到那里。
Then we return to that call site destroying the frame for f.
然后我们回到那个调用站点，销毁 f 的帧。
Now, we can finish the initialization of b, b gets 75.
现在，我们可以完成 b 的初始化，b 获得 75。
Lastly, we reached the return statement from main.
最后，我们收到了 main 的返回声明。
When we return from main, the program exits so we are done.
当我们从 main 返回时，程序会退出，这样我们就完成了。